Now that we've seen a quick glimpse at
现在已经快速了解了
the plots that are possible for a number of scenarios,
一些情景下可能的适用图表
let's go through a quick example to see the difference
我们来分析一个简单的示例
and the questions we can answer using these plots.
了解这些图表的区别以及用这些图表能够解决的问题
Consider I run a blog and I want to understand traffic on the blog.
假设我运营了博客 想了解博客的流量
For simplicity, let's just use 12 months worth of traffic.
为了简化 只统计 12 个月内的流量
If we wanted to know which month we had the most traffic,
要了解哪个月流量达到峰值
the best plot would be a bar chart or Pareto chart,
最佳的图表应该是条形图或帕累托图
as this would put the months in order from highest to lowest traffic.
因为它们可以按流量从高到低排列月份
Each bar is the amount of traffic for a particular month.
每一个条形代表特定月份的流量
It is pretty easy to see that November had the highest amount of traffic.
很容易看到 11 月份流量达到峰值
If we wanted to know if traffic was increasing over time,
要了解流量是否随时间增长
the best chart would be a line chart.
最佳的图表应该是折线图
The same information is present here,
这里呈现的信息相同
but it's easier to see that overall traffic appears to be
但是更容易看到整体的增长趋势
increasing just from the changing in the bars to a line.
只是从条形变成了折线
If we had multiple years of data,
如果有多年的数据
the line chart would also assist in identifying if
折线图也将有助于确定
particular months had higher or lower traffic than others.
是否某些特定月份的流量高于或低于其他月份
Maybe September would always be a low,
可能 9 月份流量一直较低
and November would always be higher than the other months in the year.
而 11 月份流量一直高于当年其他月份
What if we had multiple years worth of data and we wanted
如果我们有多年的数据并想了解
to know what the distribution of the number of visitors looked like.
访客数量的分布 该怎么办呢?
How frequently were there more than 2,000 visitors in a month?
一个月中访客超过 2,000 名的频率如何?
What was the most common number of visitors?
最常见的访客数量是多少呢?
From either the bar or the line chart,
条形图或折线图
this can be tough to tell.
要回答这些问题都会比较难
And neither of these questions are aimed at understanding the time component.
上述问题都没有要了解时间元素
We're interested in specifically looking at the count.
我们感兴趣的是计数
A histogram of the number of visitors looks like this,
显示访客数量的直方图看起来是这样的
and it's useful for better understanding the typical number of visitors in a month.
这有助于更好地了解一月中通常的访客数量
And the height of the bars tells us how often a certain number of visitors has occurred.
条形的高度显示了特定访客数量的发生频率
Is seeing 500 visitors on the blog a rare occurrence?
是不是很少出现 500 名访客的情况?
We can quickly see that 500 is rare.
可以快速看到 500 是罕见的数值
We can see that there are always more than 200 visitors,
可以看到 访客数量总是高于 200
but there are rarely more than 1,200 visitors.
但极少超过 1,200
The most common number of visitors is between 325 and 450.
最常见的访客数量介于 325 与 450 之间
These observations would have been much more difficult to see on those earlier plots.
使用之前的两种图表得出这些观察结果会困难得多
In the instructor notes below,
在下面的讲师注释中
I've provided a link to the Google Sheets data and
提供了 Google 电子表格的链接
charts that were used for creating the visuals in this presentation.
其中包含了本次演示使用的数据和图表
Again, because of the time component in the data,
再次提醒 由于数据包含时间元素
the line chart is probably best,
折线图可能是最好的方式
but it ultimately depends on the message that you want to convey.
但是 这最终取决于你想传递的信息
Using the same data,
使用这一份数据
we just found three ways to present the data.
我们只找到三种呈现数据的方式
The right way to visualize the data is in the way
数据可视化的正确方式
that best helps you answer your question.
应该是最能帮助你回答问题的方式